ve.com 2019-12-29

# Ve | Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Ve Global UK Limited (“ **Ve** ” or “ **we** ”) is a technology company headquartered in the UK that provides advertising and marketing solutions (“ **Services** ”) to a variety of clients who have online operations (“ **Clients** ”).

We contract directly with most of our Clients to provide our Services. We also make available our Services to certain affiliate partner networks who are able to on-provide our Services to their respective clients - in this Privacy Policy, the term “Clients” also includes these clients of our affiliate partners.

We take privacy seriously and are committed to ensuring a safe online experience. This privacy policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) explains how we use and protect personal information that we receive or collect, as set out further in this Privacy Policy.

We collect personal information about:

  * **End users who visit Client websites:** when you visit or interact with our Clients’ websites, mobile applications and services (including those of our affiliate networks) (“ **Client Sites** ”), we collect and process personal information about you. **We use this information to understand more about you and to advertise or promote our Clients’ products and services to you**. Please see Opting-out below if you wish to opt-out. You may have been redirected here because you have visited a Client Site; and
  * **Clients and other visitors to our own website:** we collect and process personal information about Client personnel who use our Services and others who visit [https://www.ve.com](https://www.ve.com/?__hstc=162943075.5b638d508e96d10d7e52d7a3f412fbdc.1580386895489.1580386895489.1580386895489.1&__hssc=162943075.1.1580386895490&__hsfp=3924935683) (“ **Our Site** ”).

This Privacy Policy is set out in three parts:

  * **Part I – Information for end users who visit Client Sites:** this section is relevant to you if you visit any of our Client Sites – this is likely to be the case where you have been redirected here from another website. Our policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it in relation to your interaction with Client Sites.
  * **Part II – Information for Clients and other visitors to our Site:** this section is relevant to Clients who use our Services and other persons who interact with Our Site. It describes what personal information we collect about you and how we use it.
  * **Part III – Miscellaneous:** this section contains further information about our use of personal information, including the rights you have.

* * *

#### How do I opt-out?

If you have visited one or more Client Sites and wish to opt-out of Ve processing your personal information, including where you wish to opt-out of Ve displaying personalised ads to you when you visit third party websites and platforms, please see How to opt-out of our use of your personal information.

* * *

#### Who are we?

Ve Global UK Limited is a company registered in England and Wales under company number 10706696 and has its registered office at White Collar Factory, Old Street Yard, London, England, EC1Y 8AF.

* * *

#### How to contact us

If you have any questions or wish to exercise your rights set out in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: Ve Data Protection Officer, White Collar Factory | Old Street Yard | London | England | EC1Y 8AF | Email: [privacy@ve.com](mailto:%20privacy@ve.com).

* * *

### Part I - Information for end users who visit Client Sites

#### What personal information do we collect and how do we collect it?

We collect the following categories of personal information from you:

  * email addresses and/or telephone numbers, if voluntarily entered into a Client Site by you (e.g. to buy a product or service, become a registered user, or sign up for marketing communications) (“ **Contact Details** ”);
  * data relating to your browsing activity through the use of cookies, web beacons and pixel tags and similar technologies deployed on Client Sites or via emails sent by Ve on behalf of Clients (“ **Behavioural Data** ”), including: 
    * IP (internet protocol) address; referring site URL (website address) where your session started, and details about your device, including type (e.g. mobile or tablet), brand, model, operating system name and version, browser name, version, language and protocol, and other unique numbers assigned to a device (e.g. IDFA on iPhone, Google adID on Android);
    * details about the pages of Client Sites visited and activities on Client Sites (e.g. products viewed or purchased, including details of purchases made and the time and duration of visits to pages of the Client’s Site), page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page;
    * using your IP address, your geolocation (e.g. postcode); and
    * events relating to ads served on you, such as the number of ads displayed to you and whether you clicked on an ad; and
  * mailing address, age and/or date of birth, gender, marital status, number of children, nationality and/or country or city of residency, telephone number and first name, in each case if input into a Client Site by you (“ **Profile Data** ”).

For more information about the technology that we use to collect Behavioural Data, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.ve.com/cookies-policy?__hstc=162943075.5b638d508e96d10d7e52d7a3f412fbdc.1580386895489.1580386895489.1580386895489.1&__hssc=162943075.1.1580386895490&__hsfp=3924935683).

We also receive Behavioural Data and Profile Data from, and may share it with, third party partners (through “cookie synching” or similar matching technologies).

We share personal information about you (including Behavioural Data and Profile Data) within the Ve group of companies to enable us to provide and improve our Services. A list of our group companies is available [here](https://www.ve.com/ve-subsidiary-list?__hstc=162943075.5b638d508e96d10d7e52d7a3f412fbdc.1580386895489.1580386895489.1580386895489.1&__hssc=162943075.1.1580386895490&__hsfp=3924935683).

We do not collect sensitive information from you (such as data relating to health or religious beliefs). Although it may be possible for us to infer certain information, such as your religious beliefs, from certain Behavioural Data that we may collect, we do not create or use segments that rely on the use of sensitive personal information for the purposes of online behavioural advertising.

* * *

#### How do we use the information we collect?

The primary purpose for which we collect personal information from you is a) to help our Clients to market, and facilitate the sale of, their products and services more effectively and/or efficiently and b) to provide a more personalised online experience for you. We achieve this by using information that we have collected (including Behavioural Data) to create inferences about your personal preferences, interests and behaviour.

Ve combines information that it collects from you across all Client Sites and uses that personal information for the benefit of each of its Clients. By way of example:

  * if Ve collects personal information when you visit Client Site A, that personal information may be used to display an ad to you, on a third party website, for products available on Client Site B.
  * if Ve collects personal information when you visit Client Site A, and you subsequently visit Client Site B and provide Client B with permission to send you marketing, Ve may use the information collected on Client Site A to personalise the content of Client B’s marketing communications that are then sent to you.

To serve you our personalised advertisements on Clients websites and provide you with a seamless online experience, we may link your identifiers on the different browsers and environments you are using (“ID Syncing”). Thanks to its ID-syncing technology, Ve is able to serve you the most relevant ads on whichever device or browser you are currently using. For this purpose, Ve uses exact linking methods by leveraging the technical data collected through out technology such as our advertising partners’ identifiers or email hash that they may pass to us. We may also receive ID-syncing information from trusted partners using diverse linking methods for the same purpose and with the same level of guarantees in terms of Privacy and Data Protection.

The purposes for which we use your personal information are described further below:

**Deliver relevant and interest-based advertising.**   

* * *

**Help our Clients analyse the effectiveness of their ad campaigns and to improve the Services we provide to Clients.**  

* * *

**Email and SMS marketing and other communications sent by Clients using Ve Services.**  

* * *

**Providing you with a customised experience when you visit Client Sites.**  

* * *

**Providing Clients with market insight and analysis.**  

* * *

**Business administration and legal compliance.**  

* * *

If we wish to use your personal information for any new purpose that is not listed above, we will, prior to using such personal information, evaluate whether it is in our legitimate interest to use the personal information for that purpose. If we determine that it is in Ve’s legitimate interest to do so, we will update this Privacy Policy to explain the new purpose. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to this Privacy Policy.

* * *

### Part II – Information for Clients and other visitors to our own Site

#### What personal information do we collect from Clients (and other people who visit Our Site) and how do we collect it?

We may collect the following categories of personal information from you:

  * name, address, e-mail address, telephone numbers, payment and credit card information, passwords, and any other personal information voluntarily submitted by you when you subscribe, register, complete forms or purchase products on Our Site, or correspond with us (via Our Site or otherwise) (“ **Voluntary Data** ”); and
  * data relating to your browsing activity through the use of cookies, web beacons and pixel tags and similar technologies (“ **Tags** ”) deployed on Our Site or emails sent by us to you, (“ **Behavioural Data** ”), including: 
    * IP (internet protocol) address; referring site URL (website address) where your session started, and details about your device, including type (e.g. mobile or tablet), brand, model, operating system name and version, browser name, version, language and protocol, and other unique numbers assigned to a device (e.g. IDFA on iPhone, Google adID on Android);
    * details about the pages of Our Site visited and activities on Our Site (e.g. products viewed or purchased, including details of purchases made and the time and duration of visits to pages of Our Site), page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page;
    * using your IP address, your geolocation (e.g. postcode); and

For more information about the technology that we use to collect Behavioural Data, please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.ve.com/cookies-policy?__hstc=162943075.5b638d508e96d10d7e52d7a3f412fbdc.1580386895489.1580386895489.1580386895489.1&__hssc=162943075.1.1580386895490&__hsfp=3924935683).

* * *

#### How do we use the information we collect from Clients (and other people who visit Our Site)?

The primary purpose for which we collect the personal information from you is to: (i) verify your identity; (ii) help us improve our Services and develop and market new products and services; (iii) carry out requests made by you on Our Sites; (iv) investigate or deal with enquiries or disputes; (v) comply with applicable laws or the requirements of a court or regulator; (vi) enforce our agreements with Clients and vendors; (vii) protect the rights, property or safety of us or third parties, including our Clients and those who visit Our Site; (viii) provide support for the provision of our Services; and (ix) use as otherwise permitted by law.

To serve you our personalised advertisements on Clients websites and provide you with a seamless online experience, we may link your identifiers on the different browsers and environments you are using (“ID Syncing”). Thanks to its ID-syncing technology, Ve is able to serve you the most relevant ads on whichever device or browser you are currently using. For this purpose, Ve uses exact linking methods by leveraging the technical data collected through out technology such as our advertising partners’ identifiers or email hash that they may pass to us. We may also receive ID-syncing information from trusted partners using diverse linking methods for the same purpose and with the same level of guarantees in terms of Privacy and Data Protection.

In particular, we may use your personal information for the following purposes:

**If you are a Client: fulfilment of Services to you.**  

* * *

**Insight and analysis.**  

* * *

**Postal marketing.**  

* * *

**Email marketing to current or prospective Clients.**  

* * *

**Business administration and legal compliance.**  

* * *

### Part III – Miscellaneous

#### Our use of cookies and similar technologies

Ve makes use of certain cookies, pixels, beacons, log files and other technologies used on Client Sites and Our Site.

Please see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.ve.com/cookies-policy?__hstc=162943075.5b638d508e96d10d7e52d7a3f412fbdc.1580386895489.1580386895489.1580386895489.1&__hssc=162943075.1.1580386895490&__hsfp=3924935683) to find out more about the cookies we use on Client Sites and Our Site.

Our Cookie Policy explains how you can manage and delete cookies which relate to Our Site.

* * *

#### How to opt-out of our use of your personal information

This section explains how you can opt-out of our use of your personal information collected in relation to your interactions with Client Sites, including how you can opt-out of us displaying personalised ads to you when you visit third party websites and platforms.

We explain below various mechanisms which you can use to opt-out of our use of your personal information in respect of Services that we provide in relation to Client Sites.

Note that some of these mechanisms are subject to various limitations and conditions. In particular some of the mechanisms require that we place a cookie on your browser in order to identify you as a person who has opted-out of our use of your personal information. If you clear cookies or reset your device settings, we will not be able to identify you as a person who has opted-out of our use of your personal information.

Retention of opt-out lists: Where you exercise your right to opt-out of receiving adverts or any personalised form of marketing, we will need to retain enough information (such as a cookie id, advertising id, or email address) in a suppression list to ensure that you do not received further marketing from us or sent by us on behalf of our Clients. This retention period will not expire, unless you contact us to advise that you would like us to, once again, send you marketing communications.

Where you opt-out using the below mechanisms, we will restrict our use of your personal information according to the opt-out that you have chosen, but we may retain your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy (for further information please see How long do we keep your personal information for?):

**Contact Us**  

* * *

**Deleting cookies on your device or browser.**  

* * *

**Using Safari’s ‘Limit Ad Tracking’ function.**  

* * *

**Using the IAB Europe’s opt-out.**  

* * *

**Native apps – Apple/iOS and Android.**  

* * *

#### Storage and sharing of personal information and transfers overseas

**Within the Ve Group.**  

* * *

**With Microsoft Azure.**  

* * *

**With other third party suppliers and partners.**  

* * *

#### How to access your information and your other rights

In addition to your right to opt-out of our use of your personal information in respect of Services which we provide in relation to Client Sites (please see How to opt-out of our use of your personal information), you have the following rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you:

**Your right of access.**  

* * *

**Your right to rectification.**  

* * *

**Your right to erasure.**  

* * *

**Your right to restrict processing.**  

* * *

**Your right to data portability.**  

* * *

**Your right to object.**  

* * *

**Your rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling.**  

* * *

**Your right to withdraw consent.**  

* * *

**Your right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority.**  

* * *

#### How do we obtain your consent?

Where our use of your personal information requires your consent, you can provide such consent:

  * at the time we collect your personal information following the instructions provided; or
  * by informing us by e-mail, post or phone using the contact details set out in this Privacy Policy.

* * *

#### Third Party Links and Services

Our Site contains links to third party websites and services. When you use a link to go from Our Site to another website or you request a service from a third party, this Privacy Policy no longer applies (except where the third party website is a Client Site, in which case Part I of this Privacy Policy applies).

* * *

#### How long do we keep your personal information for?

**In relation to personal information that we obtain in relation to your use of Client Sites, as described in Part I of this Privacy Policy.**  

* * *

**In relation to personal information that we obtain from Clients and other visitors to Our Site, as described in Part II of this Privacy Policy.**  

* * *

#### Confidentiality and security of your personal information

We are committed to keeping secure the personal information that you provide to us and we will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration.

* * *

#### Industry memberships and affiliations

Ve is a member of the European Digital Advertising Alliance (“EDAA”) and is in compliance the [EDAA’s Self- Regulatory Principles](https://www.edaa.eu/european-principles/).

* * *

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time.

* * *
